Let's go!
Ah! Again!
Here we are at Miura Fishing Port in Kanagawa Prefecture!
Yay!
Good morning!
Oh, my gosh!
Do you think we can get it?
What if there are none?
Oh, no, we can't get any more.
It smells like the ocean.
Oh, yeah!
Wow! Fish!
Fun! Fun!
Where is this boat going?
I thought we were staying somewhere around here.
You didn't.
But then I looked closer.
I thought I could walk there.
No, it's not. It's a normal walking distance.
I want to take a shot with Ty.
I'm getting the pun right.
Senpai!
Please write "Thailand" in Chinese characters in the message.
Thai pictograms too, please!
There's so many people here!
It's true!
I saw fishing.
That's great!
Thank you very much.
We've landed.
What the hell? What are they doing?
Landing!
Wow, we're here!
We're here! We're here!
We're here!
Yeah! We're here!
So, have you all arrived out of the blue?
Yes! We've arrived!
This is the Marine Fishing Forest!
And this... well, today...
We call this pond here.
This trout, ah...
This is our exclusive pond.
You can't see it right now, but there's a lot of fish down there.
There are various kinds of fish, such as kadai, waratos, and so on.
Today, we are renting these fishing lines, so we are going to fish with them.
First of all, let's learn how to use it.
This is a reel.
When you reel it in, it comes up, and this is the bail.
This one, you know, comes out with a click.
When you rewind it one more time, it stops.
When you wind this up, it comes up.
Oh!
That's how it works.
And the way you hold it is you put a teaspoon of your finger
Or you put these two right here at the base.
Yeah, it's like this.
It's very stable.
Only the index finger goes back into this.
Not that way, not your leg, your torso.
Okay. Thank you very much.
I'm going to blur it once in front of you.
Do you want to go back to sleep?
Here, put it back in. Put it back in?
Put it back. Oh, okay, it's already down.
Wait, it's already too heavy to put the fish in.
Oh, is it stuck outside?
It's stuck.
I'm so surprised. I thought I already caught it.
Just stick it in there, like a swing.
Then I let go when I think it's going the furthest.
Oh! That's great!
Try this for a second.
Just let the float wobble once
Just when it's right in the middle...
And then, boom, there it goes, there it goes.
Oh!
There you go.
Here we go.
Sounds like consciousness.
How's that?
It's good.
All right, everybody.
Shake it.
Let's go.
That's good.
I think I can do this really well.
I have this talent.
I caught it!
I caught a big taiga!
Wow! That's great!
Wow!
I'm a fool!
What does this fish want to eat? What does it want to eat now? It's important to think "What does this fish want to eat right now?
I often use artificial bait called "dumpling bait".
They also like yellow food, so we have a yellow version of this kind of food.
And this is the yellow version I usually buy when I come here.
I usually buy when I come over here.
It's got a little bit of a smell to it, like garlic and Nampula or something like that.
You can grill it like this, it's a little bit Italian, it's delicious.
with olive oil or something like that.
You know, fish that want to eat the same thing your friend next door ate.
I've done that before.
That's why the same bait catches fish all the time.
And if you use a different bait, you won't catch any fish at all.
So you can try different baits and see who catches the most fish.
That's one of the fun things about coming in a group.
What do you want today?
What do you want to eat?
Thai.
That's because today's staff was homemade.
I'm curious.
Let's see who can catch it first!
The bait's gone.
The bait!
That's about all I can take.
Thank you.
He's not a fish.
But I'm an old cell.
Rehabilitate.
Yes, sir.
Wow!
Ooh!
I'll do my best!
Come on, come on, come on.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Something's wrong.
Maybe it's not a fish. Here.
My stomach hurts.
I pushed it too hard.
This is, uh, too close.
It's stuck.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
(laughing hysterically)
I think I might have been eaten.
You feel like you just crossed the street.
I did, sort of.I did, it's like...
I'm eating summer.
I like it. I like it. I like it.
Oh, no.
Rumpler's got some serious power.
I'll show you.
How could I ever think that again?
Oh, here it comes!
One second, one second!
Aaaaahhh!
Oh no!
Oh, no!
I'm so sad... I'm so sad... I've been eaten.
It's eaten!
It's gone.
Maybe he's trying to eat it now.
It's hard.
We're all going fishing in the morning.
I told him we were going fishing.
I was told that the fish would be surprised.
I don't understand.
They're coming, they're coming, they're coming!
Kyaaa!
meee!
"Kya!
Come on, get up.
Whoo!
Whoo.
Uh-oh.
Whoo-hoo!
Wow.
This is delicious.
Mr. chicken grunt!
We caught a chicken grunt!
Mr. chicken grunt.
Wow!
Don't be a baby.
That's it.
After this...
I'm sure I'll be able to eat.
It's not coming.
I'm kind of insensitive. I don't think I'd notice if it got stuck.
I don't know. I wonder if I'll know.
That's the manager's voice.
It's in! We're in!
I'm in!
I'm the one that fell!
Wow!
Yeah!
Oh!
This one's gone, too!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
Here it comes!
It's coming! It's coming!
Oh, my God!
Why is it cracking?
Laugh it up.
Go! Go!
It's coming! It's coming!
Come on!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Where'd he go?
Whoa!
Hold on! Wait!
I'm the only one with him!
It's Sayuki and Odai!
So cute!
It was so heavy!
But still fun!
That's a great tengu!
I got it!
It's moving!
Is that it?
Well, we'll just have to trust him!
Master! Doctor!
It's not coming!
He's not coming!
Laughing.
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
I can't wait!
I want some!
I want it!
Ooohh!
He's chasing me!
It's like a tug-of-war with people!
So, do you think he'll come back?
I'd rather go to school.
If he doesn't come, I'm gonna eat him fast.
Oh no.